

I am a UX engineer with 10+ years of design experience and 3+ years of development experience, specializing in building scalable front-end products with great user experiences. I am looking for a hybrid UX designer / developer position to support between design and development.

## CONTACT

**Phone** +1 (469) 386-6307

**Email** develop.jay8675@gmail.com

Address Dallas, Texas

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/jay8675

# **PORTFOLIO**

Website jaykim-dev.netlify.app

Github github.com/jaehyung8675

**Graphic** https://bit.ly/3nlo0Cr

# **SKILLS**

**Programming** JavaScript

React

Next.js

Node.js

Express.js

Sass / SCSS HTML5

CSS

**Design** User Experience (UX)

User Interface (UI)

Product

Web

Visual

Graphic

Tools Git

Github

Visual Studio Code

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

## **EXPERIENCE**

**UX Designer** / Part-time

2017 - Present

Binnerri Presbyterian Church

Richardson, Texas

• Create all visual designs for over 400+ members to engage them in worship and events.

- Revamp 2+ websites to make them more visually and experientially accessible to customers.
- Create presentations for speakers to support their sermons and easily interact with the audience.
- Complete projects on time and deliver them to clients according to the church's schedule and goals.

**UX Engineer** 

2020 - 2023 Carrollton, Texas

**OTA World LLC** 

Led a design team to create and enhance all visual design, and maintained company websites.

- Designed and developed product pages and over 100+ merchants (Costco, Amazon, Sam's Club, Home Depot, etc.) use it to market their sites.
- Managed projects using Agile to quickly deliver products to stakeholders, vendors, and customers.
- Created global CSS to enforce a consistent style across all Shopify e-commerce sites.

#### **Graphic Designer**

2014 - 2014

Ravis's Ware House

Dallas, Texas

- Created print materials such as brochures and flyers to promote products that helped increase sales.
- Implemented lighting and design in a studio environment to produce product images.

#### **Product Designer** / Internship

2010 - 2011

Pantech Wireless, Inc.

Seoul, South Korea

- Completed 2 major projects with all mobile design processes from concept to building mock-ups.
- Explored interactions and design ideas by creating storyboards, user flows, and prototypes.
- Collaborated with team members to implement new concept designs during the summer in Japan.

#### **Unemployed** 2012 – 2013 / 2015 – 2019

Pursued to finish my education degrees, and had 5 short-term jobs as a freelance designer.

# **EDUCATION**

**University of North Texas** 

M.A. in Interaction Design Denton, Texas

Southern Methodist University

2017 - 2019

B.F.A. in Art & Graphic Design

Dallas, Texas

2020 - 2022

**Brookhaven College** 

2014 – 2017 Farmers Branch, Texas

A.A. in General Studies

2012 - 2013

**Christian For The Nations Institute** 

Dallas, Texas

Accredited Theological Degree

2006 - 2010

Hongik University

B.A. in Product Design

Sejong, South Korea